{
  "Users": [
    {
      "id": 638,
      "email": "selam@gmail.com",
      "firstName": "Mohamemd",
      "lastName": "Mohammed",
      "password": "Mohammed@123",
      "gender": "Male"
    }
  ],
  "Scores": [
    {
      "id": "HTML_CSS",
      "courseName": "HTML_CSS",
      "courseType": "Front-End",
      "courseScore": 2,
      "userId": 638
    },
    {
      "id": "Dart",
      "courseName": "Dart",
      "courseType": "Front-End",
      "courseScore": 1,
      "userId": 638
    },
    {
      "id": "Flutter",
      "courseName": "Flutter",
      "courseType": "Front-End",
      "courseScore": 2,
      "userId": 638
    },
    {
      "id": "javascript"
    },
    {
      "id": "MongoDB"
    },
    {
      "id": "Atlas_Cloud"
    },
    {
      "id": "Machine_Learning"
    },
    {
      "id": "Cloud_Computing"
    },
    {
      "id": "Analaytics"
    }
  ],
  "answers": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "answer": "Google",
      "isCorrect": true
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "answer": "May 2018",
      "isCorrect": false
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "answer": "Double",
      "isCorrect": false
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "answer": "Output",
      "isCorrect": true
    }
  ],
  "dart_practice": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Practice Dart>> Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit created by ______",
      "options": [
        "Apple",
        "Google",
        "Facebook",
        "Microsoft"
      ],
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Practice >> When google release Flutter.",
      "options": [
        "Jun 2017",
        "July 2017",
        "May 2017",
        "May 2018"
      ],
      "answer": "Jun 2017"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Practice >> A memory location that holds a single letter or number.",
      "options": [
        "Double",
        "Int",
        "Char",
        "Word"
      ],
      "answer": "Char"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Practice >> What command do you use to output data to the screen?",
      "options": [
        "Cin",
        "Count",
        "Cout",
        "Output"
      ],
      "answer": "Output"
    }
  ],
  "dart_final": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Final Dart>>  Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit created by ______",
      "options": [
        "Apple",
        "Google",
        "Facebook",
        "Microsoft"
      ],
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Final >>  When google release Flutter.",
      "options": [
        "Jun 2017",
        "July 2017",
        "May 2017",
        "May 2018"
      ],
      "answer": "Jun 2017"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Final >>  A memory location that holds a single letter or number.",
      "options": [
        "Double",
        "Int",
        "Char",
        "Word"
      ],
      "answer": "Char"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Final >>  What command do you use to output data to the screen?",
      "options": [
        "Cin",
        "Count",
        "Cout",
        "Output"
      ],
      "answer": "Output"
    }
  ],
  "HTML_CSS_practice": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Practice Html>> Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit created by ______",
      "options": [
        "Apple",
        "Google",
        "Facebook",
        "Microsoft"
      ],
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Practice >> When google release Flutter.",
      "options": [
        "Jun 2017",
        "July 2017",
        "May 2017",
        "May 2018"
      ],
      "answer": "Jun 2017"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Practice >> A memory location that holds a single letter or number.",
      "options": [
        "Double",
        "Int",
        "Char",
        "Word"
      ],
      "answer": "Char"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Practice >> What command do you use to output data to the screen?",
      "options": [
        "Cin",
        "Count",
        "Cout",
        "Output"
      ],
      "answer": "Output"
    }
  ],
  "HTML_CSS_final": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Final Html >>  Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit created by ______",
      "options": [
        "Apple",
        "Google",
        "Facebook",
        "Microsoft"
      ],
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Final >>  When google release Flutter.",
      "options": [
        "Jun 2017",
        "July 2017",
        "May 2017",
        "May 2018"
      ],
      "answer": "Jun 2017"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Final >>  A memory location that holds a single letter or number.",
      "options": [
        "Double",
        "Int",
        "Char",
        "Word"
      ],
      "answer": "Char"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Final >>  What command do you use to output data to the screen?",
      "options": [
        "Cin",
        "Count",
        "Cout",
        "Output"
      ],
      "answer": "Output"
    }
  ],
  "flutter_practice": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Practice Flutter>> Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit created by ______",
      "options": [
        "Apple",
        "Google",
        "Facebook",
        "Microsoft"
      ],
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Practice >> When google release Flutter.",
      "options": [
        "Jun 2017",
        "July 2017",
        "May 2017",
        "May 2018"
      ],
      "answer": "Jun 2017"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Practice >> A memory location that holds a single letter or number.",
      "options": [
        "Double",
        "Int",
        "Char",
        "Word"
      ],
      "answer": "Char"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Practice >> What command do you use to output data to the screen?",
      "options": [
        "Cin",
        "Count",
        "Cout",
        "Output"
      ],
      "answer": "Output"
    }
  ],
  "flutter_final": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Final Flutter >>  Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit created by ______",
      "options": [
        "Apple",
        "Google",
        "Facebook",
        "Microsoft"
      ],
      "answer": "Google"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Final >>  When google release Flutter.",
      "options": [
        "Jun 2017",
        "July 2017",
        "May 2017",
        "May 2018"
      ],
      "answer": "Jun 2017"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Final >>  A memory location that holds a single letter or number.",
      "options": [
        "Double",
        "Int",
        "Char",
        "Word"
      ],
      "answer": "Char"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Final >>  What command do you use to output data to the screen?",
      "options": [
        "Cin",
        "Count",
        "Cout",
        "Output"
      ],
      "answer": "Output"
    }
  ]
}